

Muhammad Arslan Islam

Full Stack Web Developer

Full Stack Web developer with over one year of experience. Excellent reputation for resolving problems, improving customer satisfaction, and driving overall operational improvements. Full Stack Web Developer proficient in fundamental front-end languages and server-side languages.

marslanislam.7@gmail.com

Oujranwala, Pakistan

In linkedin.com/in/muhammad-arslan-islam-123696211

SKILLS

03094985845

BOOTSTRAP CSS EXPRESS FIREBASE

GITHUB/GITLAB HTML JAVASCRIPT

MONGODB NODE JS PHP REACT JS

TAILWIND

arslanislam845.github.io/Arslan-s-Portfolio/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Full Stack Developer DEVNATION

11/2021 - 01/2022

Lahore, Pakistan

Intern Brakets

07/2021 - 09/2021

Gujranwala, Pakistan

CERTIFICATES

Full Web Development by Devnation

Problem Solving Skill by Hacker Rank

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Panjabi

Full Professional Proficiency

Urdu

Full Professional Proficiency

EDUCATION

BS in Computer ScienceCOMSATS University Islamabad

09/2019 - Present

Courses

Object-Oriented
 Programing, Machine
 Learning, Automata, Web development, Data
 Structure, Database etc..

INTERESTS

Learning New Technologies/ Tools

Traveling And Exploring Nature

Full Stack Web Development Fellow at Devnation

05/2021 - 09/2022